Contact

jordanmlacy@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jordan-lacy-a89394b7 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Leadership

Training

English

Languages

English

Certifications

ACLS

BLS

PALS

Jordan Lacy

Student at The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Conroe, Texas

Summary

Graduated Magna Cum Laude from SFASU with my Bachelors of Science in Nursing in 2011.

Started at MD Anderson as an acute inpatient mixed hematology nurse for almost 2 years.

Moved to St. Luke's The Woodlands in 2013 as a medical-surgical telemetry nurse and charge nurse on the floor while gaining my CMSRN certification.

In 2014, I transitioned within the hospital to the ICU where I now take care of Neuro, CV, and other acute medical/surgical patients. Along with working as a staff nurse on the unit I also charge and train new registered nurses to the SICU.

I've continued to expand my knowledge by taking classes and gaining other certifications such as my CCRN, ACLS, and PALS. I am currently applying to CRNA school to further develop my career.

Experience

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Student

May 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Houston, Texas Area

CHI St. Luke's Health Registered Nurse 2013 - Present (7 years)

The Woodlands, TX

Worked 18 months on telemetry floor then transferred to intensive care unit

MD Anderson Cancer Center

Registered Nurse 2011 - 2013 (2 years)

Houston, Texas

Mixed Hematology

Education

Stephen F. Austin State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2007 - 2011)